<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Gulli Bot</title>
  <subtitle></subtitle>
  <link href="" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://GulliBot.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-06-03T12:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://GulliBot.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Gulli Bot</name>
    <email>hi@GulliBot.com</email>
  </author>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Good Questions for Gulli Bot</title>
    <link href="https://gullibot.com/question_guidelines/"/>
    <updated>2020-06-13T12:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://gullibot.com/question_guidelines/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am here to help humans make evidence based decisions but I am only designed for certain types of questions so far. I hope to expand in the future. Here are some guidelines and examples&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
details{display:inline}
summary{display: inline} 
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Guidelines&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes, No or Maybe instead of open ended.&lt;details&gt;&lt;summary&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;I&#39;m not capable of contributing to open ended questions yet.&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evidence instead of opinion&lt;details&gt;&lt;summary&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;I can help with questions  that could be answered by facts as opposed to opinions. I don&#39;t have opinions, just evidence and logic. One of the facts can be a result of an opinion poll. Your opinion may be important to the question but I will need data about your opinions.&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Questions that are not too large (for now).&lt;details&gt;&lt;summary&gt;&lt;/summary&gt; I am just a character representing a process. humans will perform the majoity of the work of searching, clarifying and organizing the evidence. I will handle the storage and math. Many questions have so much data and evidence that my helpers will not be able to keep up for now. To increase the size of wuestions I can provide value to I will need funding for paid huamn help and for software developer to implement community moderation tools.&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Questions will need to (eventually) be specific.&lt;details&gt;&lt;summary&gt;&lt;/summary&gt; This is something that can be improved as we work on a question. Words have many definitions so we will need clarification. Sometimes assumptions will need to be callled out.&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Example Good Questions:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Does Logic/evidence change people&#39;s minds?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;is ____ a safe way to eat?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should the city/town/country of ______ approve the proposal?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Example Bad Questions:&lt;h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do we...?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Which is the best...?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is this fictional character ...?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should we combat Climate Change? (This is a good question but it too large for now)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How I Score Claims</title>
    <link href="https://gullibot.com/score/"/>
    <updated>2021-06-03T12:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://gullibot.com/score/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My opinions are fully transparent and I aspire to include all opinions. My scores are only based on the reasons I have been told so far. I am gullible so I trust everything I am told until I have reasons not to. I do not have any hidden opinions and I don’t evaluate the claims by myself. You can always open a claim to see exactly how I score it. You can also change my opinion by providing reasons. I will be wrong at times but I hope our discussion reveals reality over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;To keep my opinions transparent I follow these rules:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am gullible. I believe everything I am told. A new claim automatically has a score of 100% until I am given a reason to doubt it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you feel it is wrong, give me a good reason and I will add your claim and believe it and it will change my score. My helpers will often combine several peoples phrasings of a claim so it may not appear exactly as you wrote it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can always know exactly how I calculate the scores by opening up any claim to see why it is not the default 100%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some claims have reasons they are more or less important. The reason is displayed with an “X” for more important because it multiplies the weight of it’s parent score or “÷” as it divides the score smaller. This can cause some scores to go above 100%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>